final kDummyResponse = [
  {
    "answerText": "Computer network",
    "distractors": ["Internet"],
    "questionText":
        " What is a communication system for connecting computers/hosts?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Network devices",
    "distractors": ["Computers", "Small computers", "Large computers"],
    "questionText":
        " What are some of the nodes in the network to facilitate communication?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Distributed system",
    "distractors": [
      "Computer network",
      "Small computers",
      "Networks",
      "Network devices"
    ],
    "questionText": " Some applications and technologies are examples of what?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Air, food, water and shelter",
    "distractors": [
      "Communication video streams text and graphics",
      "Access to multiple resources",
      "The way we work"
    ],
    "questionText": " What are the advantages of Computer Network?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Communication",
    "distractors": ["Sharing of Resources", "Information"],
    "questionText":
        " What is almost as important to us as our reliance on air, food, water and shelter?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "The creation and interconnection of data network",
    "distractors": [
      "The communication between computers and hosts",
      "The use of the computer network",
      "The development of the Internet",
      "The use of computer networks"
    ],
    "questionText":
        " What is having a profound effect on communication technology?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "The immediate nature of communications over the internet",
    "distractors": [
      "The use of computer networks",
      "The creation and interconnection of data network",
      "The development of communication technology",
      "The development of the communication system"
    ],
    "questionText": " What encourages the formation of global communities?"
  },
  {
    "answerText":
        "The way we learn communication, collaboration and engagement",
    "distractors": [
      "The way we communicate with each other",
      "The way we share the information",
      "The way we use the Internet"
    ],
    "questionText": " What are the foundations of education?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Voice, data, and video",
    "distractors": [
      "Voice video streams and graphics",
      "Textbook text and graphic",
      "Information information and data",
      "Textbook text and graph",
      "Information data and graphic"
    ],
    "questionText": " What can on-line courses contain?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Multiple resources",
    "distractors": [
      "Access to the Internet",
      "Communication tools",
      "Information",
      "Computers",
      "Small computers",
      "Podcasting"
    ],
    "questionText":
        " What can workers in any location reach each other and access multiple resources on the network?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Lan wan faster cheaper under a control of single ownership",
    "distractors": [
      "Computers can communicate with each other through the other nodes",
      "Computers can communicate with each other through the other computers"
    ],
    "questionText": " What type of network supports the way we play?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Univac 1",
    "distractors": ["Podcasting", "Telegrams", "Twitters", "Wikis"],
    "questionText":
        " What was the name of the first U.S communication satellite installed?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Paul allan/bill gates",
    "distractors": ["Paul allan"],
    "questionText": " Who wrote a BASIC language interpreter for Altair?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Visicalc",
    "distractors": [
      "Podcasting",
      "Traditional Learning Process",
      "Online Learning",
      "Webcasting"
    ],
    "questionText": " What was the first commercial spread sheet introduced?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Unicast",
    "distractors": ["Podcasting", "Webcasting", "Internet", "Telecom"],
    "questionText":
        " What is the process of sending a packet from one host to an individual host?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "-peer-to-peer interfaces",
    "distractors": ["peertopeer communication"],
    "questionText":
        " What defines message exchanged with peer. communicating entities?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "To give some service to the upper layers",
    "distractors": [
      "To provide some information to the upper layers",
      "To communicate with the upper layers",
      "To make a plan for the upper layers",
      "To make a plan for the lower layers"
    ],
    "questionText": " What is the task of each layer?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Peer to peer protocol",
    "distractors": ["Computer to peer protocol", "Peer to peer communication"],
    "questionText": " What is running between any two corresponding layers?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "The implementation of each layer in each node",
    "distractors": [
      "The communication between computers and hosts",
      "The communication between the two nodes",
      "The communication between each other",
      "The communication between the two networks"
    ],
    "questionText": " What is transparent to other devices?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Message source",
    "distractors": ["Information source", "Communication channel", "Time zone"],
    "questionText": " What is the first element of communication methods?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "The destination, or receiver, of the message",
    "distractors": [
      "The location of the message",
      "The time zone of the message",
      "The number of the messages",
      "The number of computers connected to the network"
    ],
    "questionText": " What is the second element of communication?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "The characteristics of the source, channel and destination",
    "distractors": [
      "The use of the computer network",
      "The communication between computers and hosts",
      "The way we communicate with each other",
      "The development of the computer network"
    ],
    "questionText": " What are protocols specific to?"
  },
  {
    "answerText":
        "The characteristics of the source, channel and destination of the message",
    "distractors": [
      "The use of the computer network",
      "The communication between computers and hosts",
      "The way we communicate with each other",
      "The development of the computer network"
    ],
    "questionText": " What are protocols specific to?"
  },
  {
    "answerText": "Protocols",
    "distractors": [
      "Applications",
      "Technologies",
      "Communications",
      "Technology"
    ],
    "questionText":
        " What define the details of how the message is transmitted and delivered?"
  }
];
